{\fad(1000,0)\shad0\bord0\p1\clip(13,14,192,89)\move(102.4,201.2,102.4,137.2)\fscx11\fscy15}m 0 0 l 0 0 l 282 -337 l 469 -181 l 616 -357 l 1018 -21 l 982 23 l 623 -276 l 513 -145 l 668 -16 l 632 28 l 290 -257 l 43 37 l 43 37 l 0 0 m 306 -165 l 306 -165 l 332 -110 l 392 -101 l 349 -58 l 358 1 l 304 -27 l 250 1 l 260 -60 l 218 -102 l 278 -111 l 306 -165
m 0 0 l 0 0 l 282 -337 l 469 -181 l 616 -357 l 1018 -21 l 982 23 l 623 -276 l 513 -145 l 668 -16 l 632 28 l 290 -257 l 43 37 l 43 37 l 0 0 m 306 -165 l 306 -165 l 332 -110 l 392 -101 l 349 -58 l 358 1 l 304 -27 l 250 1 l 260 -60 l 218 -102 l 278 -111 l 306 -165
{\fsp5\shad0\bord0\fnPing Hei\b1\fs25\clip(28,87,177,117)\move(103.333,90.946,103.333,109.232)}SSK字幕組
SSK字幕組
{\fad(1000,0)\shad0\bord0\p1\fscx15\fscy15\clip(13,14,192,89)\move(102.4,201.2,102.4,137.2)\fscx11\fscy15}m 0 0 l 0 0 l 282 -337 l 469 -181 l 616 -357 l 1018 -21 l 982 23 l 623 -276 l 513 -145 l 668 -16 l 632 28 l 290 -257 l 43 37 l 43 37 l 0 0 m 306 -165 l 306 -165 l 332 -110 l 392 -101 l 349 -58 l 358 1 l 304 -27 l 250 1 l 260 -60 l 218 -102 l 278 -111 l 306 -165
m 0 0 l 0 0 l 282 -337 l 469 -181 l 616 -357 l 1018 -21 l 982 23 l 623 -276 l 513 -145 l 668 -16 l 632 28 l 290 -257 l 43 37 l 43 37 l 0 0 m 306 -165 l 306 -165 l 332 -110 l 392 -101 l 349 -58 l 358 1 l 304 -27 l 250 1 l 260 -60 l 218 -102 l 278 -111 l 306 -165
{\fsp5\shad0\bord0\fnPing Hei\b1\fs25\clip(28,87,177,117)\move(103.333,90.946,103.333,109.232)}SSK字幕組
SSK字幕組
{\c&HFBF4F8&\shad0\bord0\p1\fscx450\fscy543\move(641.333,639.333,825.333,639.333)\1a&HD1&}m 0 0 l 0 0 l 89 0 l 89 23 l 0 23
m 0 0 l 0 0 l 89 0 l 89 23 l 0 23
{\fad(500,500)\K\shad0\bord0\p1\fscx200\fscy20\c&HFBF4F8&\2c&H120B0A&\pos(364.001,634)}m 0 0 l 0 0 l 89 0 l 89 23 l 0 23
倫敦生活S01E04
字幕由SSK字幕組傾情譯制
字幕僅供學習，勿用於商
轉載請註明出處，版權歸片方所有
新浪微博@SSK字幕組
官網：www.sskzmz.com
{\shad0\bord0\fn方正兰亭纤黑_GBK\fs40\b1\c&H883A22&\frx\t(\frx360)\fry0)\pos(625.718,59.6)}翻譯   Bellatrix
翻譯   Bellatrix
{\shad0\bord0\fn方正兰亭纤黑_GBK\fs40\b1\c&H883A22&\frx\t(\frx360)\fry0\pos(625.718,59.6)}翻譯   洛貍
翻譯   洛貍
{\shad0\bord0\fn方正兰亭纤黑_GBK\fs40\b1\c&H883A22&\frx\t(\frx360)\fry0\pos(625.718,59.6)}校對   Luke  特效  CAS
校對   Luke   特效  CAS
{\shad0\bord0\fn方正兰亭纤黑_GBK\fs40\b1\c&H883A22&\frx\t(\frx360)\fry0)\pos(625.718,59.6)}壓制  hhjie 伊娃格林
壓制  hhjie 伊娃格林
{\shad0\bord0\fn方正兰亭纤黑_GBK\fs40\b1\c&H883A22&\frx\t(\frx360)\fry0)\pos(625.718,59.6)}總監  LUKE
總監  LUKE
倫敦生活
我回家了
錢放在前台了
我只想尋求一點安寧
-克萊爾
你不可能知道的 沒有人能記得住一張地圖
You cannot know this. No-one can hold a map in their head.
但我可以 還有三個路口就到了
I can! It's three turnings away.
你一定會發現自己錯了的
You're so going to get this wrong.
-快停下 -怎麼了
- Stop it. - What?
我感覺你在心裏瞧不起我的駕駛技術
I can feel you judging my driving.
我沒有瞧不起你的駕駛技術
I'm not judging your driving!
那你鬆開把手
Let go of the handle, then.
天哪 我們應該在剛剛那個路口拐彎的
Oh, we were supposed to go down that turning.
-什麼 -對呀
- What? - Yeah.
-你說還有三個路口的 -不 我漏掉了一個
- You said three turnings. - No, I missed one.
你就用一下你的手機不行麼 你手機上有衛星定位的
Just use your phone, you have a Sat Nav on your phone.
哦 天哪 就在那兒 小心 農場 就在那兒
Oh, my God, there, Mindful. Oh, God. Farm, there it is.
我們走的是對的路
We're going the right way.
我是對的
I was right.
Was right.
你知道類似於基達[男同交友軟體]的女同交友軟體叫什麼嗎
Do you know what the lesbian app for Grindr is called?
小妞定位
Twat Nav.
你不要以此取樂
Don't make this fun!
我還好 我真的還好 我感覺很好
It's OK, I'm fucking OK, I'm excellent.
-我知道我看起來有病 但我確實沒事 -好吧
- I know I seem mental, but I'm fine. - OK.
我只是
I just...
-我只是有時候需要你別 -嘲笑你
- I just sometimes need you not to... - To take the piss.
你別接我的話
Don't finish my sentences!
-嘲笑 -你和你的
- Take the piss... - Out of you and your...
你不是總知道我要說什麼 好嗎
You don't always know what I'm going to say, OK?
-對不起 當
- Sorry. - Out of...
當她在開車時取笑她
Out of her when she's driving.
我在開車時取笑我
...me while I'm driving.
對不起
I'm sorry.
是因為家裏的原因還是
Is it at home or...
因為工作還是馬丁
work or Martin?
我很好 一切都好
I'm fine, it's fine.
-馬丁一直很體貼 -真的嗎
- Martin's been lovely. - Really?
一切都好
It's fine.
我很好
I'm OK.
瘋女人
Fucking psycho.
哇 父親這次真的出大血本了
Wow! Dad really splashed out this time.
他一定是想做什麼骯髒的事
He must be about to do something awful.
不 只是因為今天是母親節
No, it's just Mother's Day.
-哦 -母親節快樂
- Oh. - Happy Mother's Day.
我們不會因為這個活動重歸於好的 對嗎
We're not supposed to bond on this, are we?
因為我不認為這樣會有個好結局
Because I really don't think that's going to end well.
我們其實不該有任何交談的
We're not supposed to talk at all.
幸虧是冥想活動 上帝都在幫我們
It's a silent retreat, God help us.
咖啡館還好嗎 你
How's everything at the cafe? You...
-你真的不用勉強找話題 -謝謝你
- You really don't have to. - Thank you.
你好
Hi.
-你好 -早上好
- Hi. - Good morning.
你好 你好
Hello, hello.
來人呀
Come on.
他們說不定覺得我們是情侶呢
They're probably going to think we're a couple.
你的想法都無可救藥了
The fact that your mind even goes there is beyond disturbing.
嘿 我們會成為很可愛的一對的
Hey! We'd make a really cute couple.
蕩婦
'Sluts!'
有事嗎
Yes?
今天我會死在這兒的 我們都會被姦殺的
I'm going to die here. We're going to be raped and die.
每一片雲
Every cloud...
哦 把門打開啊 難道永遠都不能
Oh, just open the fucking door. It's been fucking forev...
歡迎
Welcome.
-非常感謝 -你好
- Thank you so much. - Hi. Yeah.
這裏真不錯
It's really wonderful.
-地板真好看 -非凡的精氣神
- Really beautiful grounds. - Extraordinary energy, yeah.
有人請你們兩位來我們這裏做冥想 你們倆真幸運
I see you've been gifted this retreat. How lucky you both are.
我希望這個週末之後 你們會感到靈魂得以安放 精神受到鼓舞
I hope after this weekend, you will feel rested, inspired.
-你們這裏有無線網嗎 -沒有
- Do you have Wi-Fi? - No.
呃 你們是要兩張單人床還是一張雙人床
Erm, would you like two single beds or a double?
-兩個單人床 -一個雙人床謝謝
- Two singles. - A double, please.
-事實上 你有沒有分開來的房間 -恐怕沒有
- Actually, do you have a separate room? - I'm afraid not.
在這裏每個人都要和別人同住 這是共同生活的一部分
Everyone has to share here. It's part of the communal...
那就單人床吧 你們早上有報紙嗎
Singles, then. Do you get newspapers in the morning?
不 我們試著在你們住宿期間
No, we try to keep the outside world on the outside
將外界信息隔絕在外
during your stay here.
我承諾 你們最終會感激這點的
You'll appreciate it in the end, I promise.
-好 這是你們的鑰匙 -謝謝
- So, here is your key. - Thank you.
-祝你們度過一個放鬆的週末 -你也是
- You have a restful weekend. - You too.
-哇哦 沒有報紙 -你又不讀報
- Wow, no papers. - You don't read the news.
-不 我讀 -昨天發生了什麼事
- Yes, I do! - What happened yesterday?
黏糊糊的舊白牛仔褲和一隻小狗卡在了風扇裏
Sting wore white jeans and a puppy got stuck in a fan.
真是個大日子
Big day.
-那個是幹什麼的 -塗我的脖子和胸
- What's that for? - My neck and chest.
-那個是幹什麼的 -塗我的腿和膝蓋
- What's that for? - My legs and knees.
-那個是幹什麼的 -塗我的發尾
- What's that for? - Ends of my hair.
-那是幹什麼的 -塗我的眼袋
- What's that? - For my under-eyes.
-那是幹什麼的 -塗我的臉和全身
- What's that? - That is for my face and body.
如果有個人把這些都偷走了 你會怎麼辦
What would you do if someone stole all of those?
我會自殺
I'd kill myself.
為什麼這裏沒有插座
Why are there no plug sockets in here?
別碰我的東西
Don't touch my stuff.
-這些是幹什麼的 -沒什麼
- What are these for? - Nothing.
-嗯 -怎麼了
- Mm-hm. - What?
沒什麼 只是
Well, it's just...
你為什麼要帶這麼小的電池
Why would you bring such tiny batteries?
我只是準備得充分而已
I'm just prepared.
只是我曾經
Just I've only ever...
-看見遙控器裏用過 -對
- seen them used for remote controls. - Yes.
-或者鬧鐘里 -對
- Or alarm clocks. - Yes, all right.
-或者震動棒 -對 就是這個
- And vibrators. - Yes! All right!
你根本不用申請分開的房間
You didn't have to ask for a separate room!
什麼
What?
如果你想自慰 我可以給你空間的
If you want to have a wank, I can give you some space.
哦 我的天哪
Oh, my God!
不是的 如果你需要花十分鐘
No, if you want to take ten minutes,
我會去浴室給我的手腕擦點霜
I'll go into the bathroom and moisturise my wrists for a bit.
-你真幼稚 -我還沒完呢
- You are so immature! - Oh, give it a minute.
哦 天哪 嚴肅點
Oh, God. Seriously!
你腦子有什麼問題
- What is wrong with your insides?
你為什麼要帶這些小電池
- Why did you bring the tiny batteries?
你這個天才
You're a genius.
總能發現備用品在哪裏
Always know where the reserves are.
放下你的過去
Let go of your past.
-說到點子上了 -現在是時候放下了
- Bit on the nose. - Now is the time to let it go.
開放你的感官 閉上嘴 享受現在
Open up your senses, close your mouth and live now.
歡迎來到只對女性開放的寂靜之息冥想活動
Welcome to the female-only Breath Of Silence retreat.
女性們應該沉默
Women don't speak.
呃 對不起 我覺得我應該在
Erm, sorry. I think I'm meant to be at...
-「可恨的蕩婦」 -那個活動
- 'Fucking sluts!' - ...that one.
可惜了
Shame.
是的 現在最重要的問題是你們為什麼在這裏
Yes, the first major consideration is why are you here?
現場誰能回答這個問題
Can anyone here answer that question?
我想隔絕外面的噪音 重新回到我的內心
I want to shut the noise out and reconnect to my inner thoughts
去獲取更多關於自身的感覺
on the road to feeling more at one with myself.
不錯的態度
Excellent attitude.
那麼 你來對了地方
Well, you're in the right place.
這個週末有關於專注內心
And this weekend is about being mindful.
關於將你的聲音留在頭腦裏
It's about leaving your voice in your head...
將你的想法困在頭顱中
...and trapping your thoughts in your skull.
想像你的大腦中有一個思維監獄
Think of it as a thought prison in your mind.
首先 我們將會教你如何呼吸
Firstly, we're going to teach you how to breathe.
接著我們會有一次短暫的冥想
Then we will have a short meditation,
然後我們會在參加枯燥任務的過程中尋找到我們心靈的庇護所
then we will find our sanctuary in the partaking of menial tasks,
這一切都在絕對的寂靜中
all in perfect silence.
原則性的規定就是不要講話
Principal rules are no talking.
如果你想和我們其中一位監管員交流
If you need to communicate with any of our other superiors,
你可以寫在那個黑板上
you can write on that board.
在任何你想交流的情況下
Under no other circumstances must you communicate,
甚至是想互相交流的時候
even with each other.
-如果是緊急情況呢 -感謝你們今天到場
- What about an emergency? - Thank you all for coming here today.
不管發生了什麼 一點聲音都不能發出
No matter what happens, a word must not be heard.
噓
Shh!
「蕩婦」
'Slut!'
「賤人」
'Bitch!'
「賤人 賤人」
'Bitch, bitch!'
可恨的賤人 你就是一坨屎
Fucking bitch! You fucking piece of shit.
過來 過來 到我這兒來
Back here! Back here, back to me. Back to me.
好的 現在 不管那些怨言是因為什麼 是因為你的教養也好
All right, now, wherever it's come from... your upbringing,
或是因為你和女人的經歷也罷 現在是時候改變一下了
your experiences with women, now is the time to turn that around.
重裝你的思想
To reprogram your mind,
你的身體 你的嘴
your body and your mouth.
成為一個更好的男人
To be the better... man.
好嗎
All right?
那麼 這位是帕特希亞
So, this... is Patricia.
好嗎 她是個朋友
Yeah? She's a friend.
現在 帕特希亞剛剛在工作中獲得升職
Now, Patricia has just earned a promotion at work,
打敗了其他六位候選者
beating over six other candidates.
她是獲得這個這個職位最年輕的人
She's the youngest person to ever achieve this role.
我們在遇見她的時候不能說什麼
What should we not say when we meet her?
-聰明的小不點 -好極了
- Clever little munchkin? - Excellent.
-你為誰口交才得到的這個職位 -好
- Who did you blow to get that job? - OK.
-蕩婦 你這個可惡的蠢蕩婦 -好的
- Slut, you fucking stupid slut. - OK.
好的
Ok.
我們應當對她說什麼呢
What should we say to her?
嗯
Hmm?
-做的不錯 帕特希亞 -非常好
- Well done, Patricia. - Very good.
「做的不錯 帕特希亞」
"Well done, Patricia."
請離開
Please leave.
-變態 -蕩婦
- Perv. - Slut.
哇哦
Wow!
做的不錯 帕特希亞
Well done, Patricia.
蕩婦
Slut!
夥計們 沒事
Guys, it's OK.
凱斯 來
Keith, come.
我的天哪 對不起女士 你不能來這裏
Oh, my God. Excuse me, miss, you can't be here.
-好的 -你真的不能到這裏來
- OK. - You really can't be here.
這會讓他們感覺不好的 求你了
It's a feel-no-good. Please.
現在 舉起你們的手
And now, hands up.
掌心相對
Mirror your palms.
看著對方的眼睛
Look each other in the eye, and...
然後觸碰
...touch.
絕對是她最可怕的噩夢
Literally her worst nightmare.
噁
Eugh!
你還好嗎
Are you all right?
-和我說說 -沒什麼
- Talk to me. - It's nothing.
天哪
God.
我感覺不到我的腳了
I can't feel my feet.
你還記得我們曾經玩「從頭到腳」嗎
Do you remember we used to go top-to-toe?
現在的孩子都很怪
Now kids are so weird.
-我們以前總是玩那個遊戲
- We used to do that all the time.
-對呀 我們那時才十歲 也很可愛
- Yeah, when we were ten and cute.
-現在我們三十歲了 而且憤世嫉俗 -我不是在說我們
- Now we're 30 and angry. - I'm not suggesting that we...
就是別說了 行嗎
Just don't, OK?
別偷我的東西了
Stop stealing my things!
我只是試試它好不好使
I'm just checking it's working.
哦 它絕對好使
Oh, it's working, it's definitely working.
噓
'Shh!'
玩的開心
Have fun.
這真是個十分體貼的禮物 謝謝你
It's actually a really thoughtful present. Thank you.
馬丁給我了那個小雕塑
And Martin getting me that sculpture.
他為了買到這個東西肯定花了不少心血
He must have bent over backwards to get something like that.
我覺得自己好幸運
I feel very lucky.
我跟你說啊
I have to tell you something.
什麼
What?
那個雕像是我從別人的工作室順手拿的
I stole that sculpture from a certain somebody's studio
然後想通過馬丁找個買主
and then I tried to sell it through Martin,
不過馬丁把雕像留下了 還送給了你
but Martin took it and gave it to you.
這事你可別當著老爸
Just don't put it pride of place when Dad...
呃 當著他們的面說
well, when they come over.
-好嗎 因為 -好
- OK? Because... - Right.
克萊爾
Claire!
-克萊爾 -噓 快睡吧
- Claire! - Shh. Go to sleep.
該死
Shit.
-我們越快適應 -啊
- The sooner we get on... - Ah.
我們越快適應 就能越快離開這裏
The sooner we get on with it, the sooner we are out of here.
-這外套真好看 -謝啦
- That's a really nice outfit. - Thanks.
深入挖掘你的回憶
Delve into your past.
想想你無法釋懷的東西
Think of something you can't let go of.
一段噪音
A moment of noise.
一個緊張時刻
A moment of tension.
-不要 -現在
- Not for now. - Now...
想想你覺得內心平靜的時刻
...A moment when you were peaceful.
要是你能隨心所欲
If you could change
改變世上的任何東西 你想改變什麼
anything in the whole world, what would it be?
我的大腿
My thighs.
整個世界你就想改變這個
In the whole world?
可別跟別人說 那你呢
Don't tell anyone I said that. You?
我一直對自己的顏值挺不滿的
I've always been insecure about my face.
-你明明知道 -我知道
- You know that. - I know.
-你不用不滿啊 -謝了 不過
- You shouldn't. - Thank you, but...
不啊 真的 你的鼻子一點問題都沒有
No, seriously, there's nothing wrong with your nose.
-我的意思是 你的臉 -你再說一遍
- I mean, there's nothing wrong... - Say that again?
-我的意思是 你的臉 -你說什麼
- I mean, there's nothing wrong... - What?
不知道
I don't know.
-啊 -哦天
- Ah! - Oh, my God.
我總說錯話
I always say the wrong thing!
啊 啊
Ah! Agh!
好燙
Hot.
這是幹嘛 我在自己家都不幹這些活的
What is this? I don't even do this in my own home.
道理很簡單
Well, it's very simple.
我們是花錢給人家做掃除 還不能出聲
We've paid them to let us clean their house in silence.
老天
Jesus.
我不想像老師一樣批評你們
I don't want to come down on you like a schoolteacher,
但是你們明目張膽違反這裏的規則
but I'm afraid your flagrant lack of respect for the one rule
恐怕已經影響到其他學生了
that we have here is now affecting the other students.
-顧客 -你是說囚犯嗎
- Clients. - Inmates?
-或者說是清潔工吧 -參與者
- Cleaners? - Participants!
你們對這個活動有什麼不滿嗎
Do you have a problem with the programme?
我建議你們在這裏靜坐一小時
I suggest you try sitting here in silence for the next hour.
對你們有好處的
It will benefit you.
我以靈魂發誓 肯定有好處
I swear by my soul, it will.
我翻你的包來著
I went through your bag.
什麼
What?
我什麼也沒找到 所以你得
I couldn't find anything, so you're just going to have
親自告訴我你到底怎麼了
to tell me what's going on with you.
說話 不然我就喊啦
Talk! Or I will scream.
我獲得了升職到芬蘭的機會
I got the Finland promotion.
什麼升職到芬蘭
What Finland promotion?
你怎麼還問 我都跟你說過了
How can you ask that? I've told you about it!
我知道 挺好的呀
I know the Finland promotion, that's amazing.
謝謝
Thank you.
這是不是就意味著你現在是土豪啦 抱大腿
Does that mean you're a millionaire now? Handy.
別傻了
Don't be ridiculous.
是啊 會是
Yes, it would.
所以你有錢還不開心嗎
All that money makes you cry?
我準備拒絕掉
I'm turning it down.
什麼
What?
為什麼 因為馬丁唄
Why? Martin?
馬丁說這樣對傑克不公平
Martin says it would be unfair on Jake.
傑克是她的繼子 他真是個怪胎
Jake's her stepson, he's really weird,
從癥狀來看是這樣 但是沒人這麼說
probably clinically, but no-one really talks about that.
要是她有超過一天不在身邊 他就嚇尿了
He freaks out if she's gone for longer than a day
他甚至想跟她一起洗澡
and he's got this thing about trying to get in the bath with her.
不 不 不 傑克 不行
No, no. No, Jake. No!
他都十五歲了
He's 15.
-他又不是你兒子 -重點不在這
- He's not your son. - That's not the point.
-去吧 -我就知道你會這麼說
- Go! - I knew you'd say that.
-你不是一直想要這個機會嗎 -我知道
- This is what you've always wanted. - I know.
-再也不用穿職業裝 還到處都是雪 -我知道
- No more power suits, fuckload of snow. - I know.
那地方很適合你這種冷血動物啊
Perfect place for your cold, cold heart.
我知道 但我做不到
I know, I can't!
-我有我的責任 -噢 別鬧了
- I have responsibilities. - Oh, come on.
別讓別人妨礙你追求理想
Don't let other people get in the way of what you really want.
芬蘭就是你的理想
Finland is what you really want.
我丈夫可不是什麼「別人」 好嗎
My husband isn't "Other people", OK?
我丈夫就是我的生活支柱
My husband is my life.
你丈夫在你生日那天還想親我來著
Your husband tried to kiss me on your birthday.
真的嗎
Did he?
蕩婦
'Sluts!'
Slut!
-蕩婦 -不錯 不錯
- Slut! - Lovely, lovely.
好了嗎
Ok?
站起來 我們要說「對不起 帕特希亞」
Up on your feet. We're going to say, "Sorry, Patricia."
對不起 帕特希亞
Sorry, Patricia.
很好 給自己鼓鼓掌吧
Lovely, give yourselves a round of applause.
好了 各位 做得很好
All right, guys. Well done.
我們要以嶄新的面貌回到屋裏 好嗎
We are going to head back to that house better men, yeah?
很好 不錯 很棒
Well done, good work. Great stuff.
-對 嶄新的面貌 -很好
- Yeah, a new man. - Well done.
繼續
Go on.
你可以的
You can do it.
加油
You're ready.
嗯 我覺得我認出你了
Yeah, I... thought I recognised you.
好吧
Fair enough.
這樣就好
Probably for the best.
所以 你的生意
So, is your business...
還好嗎
...surviving?
對不起
I'm sorry.
噢 我不想抽了
No, I don't want that.
所以 你是在
So, you're doing the whole...
沉默訓練營之類的
silent escape thing.
看來是的
Indeed.
還好嗎
Going well?
我摸了一個同事的胸
I touched a colleague's breast.
不止一次
More than once.
在派對上 我
At a party, I...
他們讓我去參加訓練營
They asked me to go on a workshop to...
我就是個非常
I'm just a very...
令人失望的人
...disappointing man.
不了 謝了 我正在戒呢
No, thanks, I'm trying to quit.
另一方面 那些人
Those, on the other hand.
他們一直問我「你想從訓練營得到什麼」
They keep asking me, "What do you want from this workshop?
「你想要什麼」
"What do you want?"
我才不會告訴他們我想要什麼
I'm not telling them what I want.
我想回家
I want to move back home.
我想抱老婆
I want to hug my wife.
保護孩子 保護女兒
Protect my children, protect my daughter.
我想重新開始
I want to move on.
我想道歉
I want to apologise.
跟所有人道歉
To everyone.
想去電影院
Want to go to the theatre.
我想把乾淨的杯子從洗碗機裏拿出來
I want to take clean cups out of the dishwasher
放到我家的壁櫥裏
and put them in the cupboard at home...
第二天早上 我想看著我老婆用這些杯子喝水
...and the next morning, I want to watch my wife drink from them.
我想讓她開心
And I want to make her feel good.
我想讓她再次達到高潮
I want to make her orgasm again.
一遍又一遍
And again.
真的
Truly.
我只是想哭
I just want to cry.
一直都是
All the time.
克萊爾
Claire?
你們看見我姐姐沒有
Have you seen my sister?
你好 我是小波
'Hi, this is Boo.
現在無法接電話
'I can't come to the phone right now,
請留言
'but please leave me a messiagio,
稍後我會打給你
'and I'll get back to you.'
要是有人把電話線拔了就好了
Someone should probably disconnect that.